<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lotus Docs Example Site</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/</link><description>Recent content on Lotus Docs Example Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 23:26:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>À propos</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/about/</guid><description>Bienvenue dans notre projet de documentation technique Ce projet fait partie de notre cours de génie informatique. Il vous offre une aide pratique pour construire et gérer des sites Web de documentation technique. Nous utilisons des technologies Web modernes et suivons les meilleures pratiques de l&amp;rsquo;industrie pour vous aider à bien apprendre la documentation technique.
Ce que nous visons à faire Nous sommes ici pour aider les développeurs, nouveaux et expérimentés, à comprendre comment créer des sites Web de documentation.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/about/</guid><description>Welcome to Our Technical Documentation Project linkThis project is part of our Informatics Engineering course. It gives you practical help to build and manage websites for technical documentation. We use modern web technologies and follow industry best practices to help you learn technical documentation well.
What We Aim to Do linkWe are here to help both new and seasoned developers understand how to create documentation websites. Our project includes everything from managing content and designing, to following accessibility standards and working with backend technologies.</description></item><item><title>About Page Implementation</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/about-implement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/about-implement/</guid><description>Introduction linkIn this page it is possible to follow a step by step guide that aims to educate the reader on how to make the color picker page in this website.
Set up link Install Hugo and Go
If you haven’t installed Hugo and Go, you can go see the installation guidelines provided in Hugo Installation. If you do already have them installed you can skip this step and go directly to the next one.</description></item><item><title>Color Picker Page implementation</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/color-picking-implementation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/color-picking-implementation/</guid><description>Introduction linkIn this page it is possible to follow a step by step guide that aims to educate the reader on how to make a the olor picker page in this website.
Set up link Install Hugo and Go
If you haven’t installed Hugo and Go, you can go see the installation guidelines provided in Hugo Installation. If you do already have them installed you can skip this step and go directly to the next one.</description></item><item><title>Color Picking</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/color-picking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/color-picking/</guid><description>Customizing the Top Header with Color Pickers linkWe&amp;rsquo;ve introduced an interactive feature to the top header of our site, allowing users to personalize their experience by changing the background and font colors.
This guide will walk you through the changes made to top-header.html to add this functionality.
Introduction linkThe top header of our website now includes two color pickers: one for the background color and another for the font color.</description></item><item><title>Deployment</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/deployment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/deployment/</guid><description>Requirements git Go ≥ v1.19 Hugo ≥ v0.100.0 (Extended Version) Install Hugo Install the Hugo CLI, using the specific instructions for your operating system below:
LinuxHomebrew (macOS)Windows (Chocolatey)Windows (Scoop)Your Linux distro’s package manager may include Hugo. If this is the case, install it directly using your distro’s package manager – for instance, in Ubuntu, run the following command. This will install the extended edition of Hugo:</description></item><item><title>Deployment</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/deployment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/deployment/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Deployment</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/deployment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/deployment/</guid><description>Requirements git Go ≥ v1.19 Hugo ≥ v0.100.0 (Extended Version) Install Hugo Install the Hugo CLI, using the specific instructions for your operating system below:
LinuxHomebrew (macOS)Windows (Chocolatey)Windows (Scoop)Your Linux distro’s package manager may include Hugo. If this is the case, install it directly using your distro’s package manager – for instance, in Ubuntu, run the following command. This will install the extended edition of Hugo:</description></item><item><title>Farbauswahl</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/color-picking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/color-picking/</guid><description>Anpassung des oberen Headers mit Farbauswahl Wir haben eine interaktive Funktion im oberen Header unserer Website eingeführt, mit der Benutzer ihr Erlebnis personalisieren können, indem sie die Hintergrund- und Schriftfarben ändern.
Dieser Leitfaden führt Sie durch die Änderungen, die an top-header.html vorgenommen wurden, um diese Funktion hinzuzufügen.
Einführung Der obere Header unserer Website enthält jetzt zwei Farbauswähler: einen für die Hintergrundfarbe und einen anderen für die Schriftfarbe.
Diese Ergänzung verbessert das Benutzerengagement, indem sie eine anpassbarere Benutzeroberfläche bietet.</description></item><item><title>Implémentation de la page de sélection de couleur</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/color-picking-implementation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/color-picking-implementation/</guid><description>Introduction Sur cette page, il est possible de suivre un guide étape par étape qui vise à éduquer le lecteur sur la façon de créer la page de sélection de couleur sur ce site Web.
Configuration Installer Hugo et Go
Si vous n&amp;rsquo;avez pas encore installé Hugo et Go, vous pouvez consulter les directives d&amp;rsquo;installation fournies dans Installation de Hugo. Si vous les avez déjà installés, vous pouvez passer cette étape et passer directement à la suivante.</description></item><item><title>Implementierung der Farbauswahlseite</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/color-picking-implementation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/color-picking-implementation/</guid><description>Einführung In dieser Seite ist es möglich, einem schrittweisen Leitfaden zu folgen, der den Leser darüber informiert, wie die Farbauswahlseite auf dieser Website erstellt wird.
Einrichtung Hugo und Go installieren
Wenn Sie Hugo und Go noch nicht installiert haben, können Sie die Installationsanleitungen unter Hugo Installation einsehen. Wenn Sie sie bereits installiert haben, können Sie diesen Schritt überspringen und direkt zum nächsten übergehen.
Vergessen Sie nicht die Voraussetzungen. Sie sollten den folgenden Befehl oder ähnliches benötigen: choco install hugo-extended (Windows) oder brew install hugo (Mac) zum Beispiel.</description></item><item><title>Implementierung der Über uns-Seite</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/about-implement-de/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/about-implement-de/</guid><description>Einleitung Auf dieser Seite können Sie einer schrittweisen Anleitung folgen, die darauf abzielt, den Leser darüber zu informieren, wie die Farbwähler-Seite auf dieser Website erstellt wird.
Einrichtung Installieren Sie Hugo und Go
Wenn Sie Hugo und Go noch nicht installiert haben, können Sie die Installationsanleitungen unter Hugo Installation einsehen. Wenn Sie sie bereits installiert haben, können Sie diesen Schritt überspringen und direkt zum nächsten übergehen.
Vergessen Sie nicht die Voraussetzungen. Sie benötigen den folgenden oder einen ähnlichen Befehl: choco install hugo-extended (Windows) oder brew install hugo (Mac).</description></item><item><title>Mise en Place de la Page À Propos</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/about-implement-fr/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/about-implement-fr/</guid><description>Introduction Sur cette page, il est possible de suivre un guide étape par étape qui vise à éduquer le lecteur sur la manière de créer la page de sélection de couleur sur ce site web.
Configuration Installer Hugo et Go
Si vous n&amp;rsquo;avez pas encore installé Hugo et Go, vous pouvez consulter les instructions d&amp;rsquo;installation fournies dans Installation de Hugo. Si vous les avez déjà installés, vous pouvez passer cette étape et aller directement à la suivante.</description></item><item><title>Sélection des couleurs</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/color-picking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/color-picking/</guid><description>Personnalisation de l&amp;rsquo;en-tête supérieur avec des sélecteurs de couleur Nous avons introduit une fonctionnalité interactive dans l&amp;rsquo;en-tête supérieur de notre site, permettant aux utilisateurs de personnaliser leur expérience en changeant les couleurs de fond et de police.
Ce guide vous guidera à travers les modifications apportées à top-header.html pour ajouter cette fonctionnalité.
Introduction L&amp;rsquo;en-tête supérieur de notre site Web comprend désormais deux sélecteurs de couleur : un pour la couleur de fond et un autre pour la couleur de la police.</description></item><item><title>Setup</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/setup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/setup/</guid><description>Requirements git Go ≥ v1.19 Hugo ≥ v0.100.0 (Extended Version) Install Hugo Install the Hugo CLI, using the specific instructions for your operating system below:
LinuxHomebrew (macOS)Windows (Chocolatey)Windows (Scoop)Your Linux distro’s package manager may include Hugo. If this is the case, install it directly using your distro’s package manager – for instance, in Ubuntu, run the following command. This will install the extended edition of Hugo:</description></item><item><title>Setup</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/setup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/docs/setup/</guid><description>Requirements link git Go ≥ v1.19 Hugo ≥ v0.100.0 (Extended Version) Install Hugo linkInstall the Hugo CLI, using the specific instructions for your operating system below:
LinuxHomebrew (macOS)Windows (Chocolatey)Windows (Scoop)Your Linux distro’s package manager may include Hugo. If this is the case, install it directly using your distro’s package manager – for instance, in Ubuntu, run the following command. This will install the extended edition of Hugo:</description></item><item><title>Setup</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/setup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/fr/docs/setup/</guid><description>Requirements git Go ≥ v1.19 Hugo ≥ v0.100.0 (Extended Version) Install Hugo Install the Hugo CLI, using the specific instructions for your operating system below:
LinuxHomebrew (macOS)Windows (Chocolatey)Windows (Scoop)Your Linux distro’s package manager may include Hugo. If this is the case, install it directly using your distro’s package manager – for instance, in Ubuntu, run the following command. This will install the extended edition of Hugo:</description></item><item><title>Über</title><link>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>$%7BDEPLOY_PRIME_URL%7D/de/docs/about/</guid><description>Willkommen bei unserem Projekt zur technischen Dokumentation Dieses Projekt ist Teil unseres Kurses für Informatiktechnik. Es bietet Ihnen praktische Hilfe beim Aufbau und der Verwaltung von Websites für technische Dokumentationen. Wir verwenden moderne Webtechnologien und folgen den besten Praktiken der Branche, um Ihnen zu helfen, technische Dokumentation gut zu erlernen.
Was wir erreichen wollen Wir sind hier, um sowohl neuen als auch erfahrenen Entwicklern zu helfen, den Aufbau von Dokumentationswebsites zu verstehen.</description></item></channel></rss>