<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on Lotus Docs Example Site</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on Lotus Docs Example Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:40:16 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Our Technical Documentation Project linkThis project is part of our Informatics Engineering course. It gives you practical help to build and manage websites for technical documentation. We use modern web technologies and follow industry best practices to help you learn technical documentation well.&#xA;What We Aim to Do linkWe are here to help both new and seasoned developers understand how to create documentation websites. Our project includes everything from managing content and designing, to following accessibility standards and working with backend technologies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Page Implementation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/about-implement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/about-implement/</guid>
      <description>Introduction linkIn this page it is possible to follow a step by step guide that aims to educate the reader on how to make the color picker page in this website.&#xA;Set up link Install Hugo and Go&#xA;If you haven’t installed Hugo and Go, you can go see the installation guidelines provided in Hugo Installation. If you do already have them installed you can skip this step and go directly to the next one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Picker Page implementation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/color-picking-implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/color-picking-implementation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction linkIn this page it is possible to follow a step by step guide that aims to educate the reader on how to make a the olor picker page in this website.&#xA;Set up link Install Hugo and Go&#xA;If you haven’t installed Hugo and Go, you can go see the installation guidelines provided in Hugo Installation. If you do already have them installed you can skip this step and go directly to the next one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Picking</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/color-picking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/color-picking/</guid>
      <description>Customizing the Top Header with Color Pickers linkWe&amp;rsquo;ve introduced an interactive feature to the top header of our site, allowing users to personalize their experience by changing the background and font colors.&#xA;This guide will walk you through the changes made to top-header.html to add this functionality. In the end you should be able to recreate this functionality.&#xA;Introduction linkThe top header of our website now includes two color pickers: one for the background color and another for the font color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/deployment/</guid>
      <description>Deploying a Hugo Website with Netlify linkThis guide will help you deploy your Hugo website using Netlify. It is a platform for hosting static websites.&#xA;Before You Start linkMake sure you have:&#xA;A Hugo website project ready. Signed up for a Netlify account. Installed Hugo on your computer. Steps linkSign Up for Netlify linkCreate an account on Netlify, or login to an existent account.&#xA;Add Your Site to Netlify linkGo to the Netlify sites page and click “New site from Git.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:37:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/setup/</guid>
      <description>Requirements link git Go ≥ v1.19 Hugo ≥ v0.100.0 (Extended Version) Install Hugo linkInstall the Hugo CLI, using the specific instructions for your operating system below:&#xA;Linux&#xD;Homebrew (macOS)&#xD;Windows (Chocolatey)&#xD;Windows (Scoop)&#xD;Your Linux distro’s package manager may include Hugo. If this is the case, install it directly using your distro’s package manager – for instance, in Ubuntu, run the following command. This will install the extended edition of Hugo:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
